Mateo Dundek



mateo.dundek94@gmail.com



+447885499412



linkedin.com/in/mateo-dundek-5bb39014b

Summary

I am 29 years old from Croatia.

Currently working full-time as a security officer and in my free time I am taking Frontend Software Engineer courses: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.

Given an opportunity to work as a Frontend Software Developer, I would do my best to catch up with company and team requirements and even take extra courses if needed.

Experience

Security Officer

G4S

Sep 2022 - Present (8 months)

Security and customer service

Sous Chef

Oakman Inns & Restaurants Ltd

Aug 2021 - Jun 2022 (11 months)

Preparing and cooking food, got promoted to Sous chef in February 2022

Chef

Mitchells & Butlers PLC

Aug 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Preparing and cooking food

Frankie Chef

Frankie & Benny's

Jan 2019 - Jul 2020 (1 year 7 months)

Counting stock, perparing and cooking food

Repairer

Plava Laguna

Jul 2018 - Nov 2018 (5 months)

Maintenance of pool techniques

Factory Worker

ESCO Pte. Ltd.

Oct 2017 - Mar 2018 (6 months)

Quality management and control

#POB Factory Worker

#POB

Mar 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year 8 months) Worker on the welding line and machine maintenance

Electrician

ELEKTROMETAL

Sep 2015 - Dec 2015 (4 months) Company went bankrupt

Education



Technical School Bjelovar

Skills

css • html • microsoft office • microsoft windows • Software • Hardware • React.js • Customer Service • JavaScript